If your vehicle is also insured
with ICICI LBR or you are
thinking of getting your vehicle insured with ICICI LB,
then watch this video completely once.
As you saw in my previous videos
that my Skod Away caught fire
and ICICI LBA rejected my claim
visit saying that it has after market
fitment.  For which
I had filed a case against ICICI Lombard in the Lok Adalat.
If you haven't seen my previous videos, there's
a link in the description.
Go and see it once.  So my last hearing was on 12th November 2025,
what happened in the Lok Adalat?  Let us know.  Hello
friends, I hope you all are well
and first of all I
want to apologize to all of you that I am uploading this video so late.
I read your comments
in which you were asking what happened
in the Lok Adalat hearing on 12th November
?  So let me tell you that during the hearing on 12th November,
his advocate came on behalf of ICIC Lobard and he submitted his power of attorney.
This means ICICI Lombard has
acknowledged our case and their
advocates will fight on their behalf.  Now
what will be the next step that the Lok Court has
given us a new date of 24 January 2026 in
which we will have reconciliation talks means
conciliation proceedings.  What will happen in that is that if
both the parties are ready to reach an
agreement among themselves in front of the panel in ICICI Labord
, if they are ready to do an out of the court
settlement, then we will have that
discussion.  If we settle it among ourselves then
that case will be solved there itself
and its result will come as soon as possible.
If any one of us parties does
not accept it, does
not settle the matter, then the case will be accepted back in the Lok Adalat
and we will
get a new hearing date in which the Lok Adalat
will conduct the full hearing and will give its decision.
So, it is hoped that on January 24, 2026, both the
parties will reach an agreement among themselves and this
settlement should happen and the case should be resolved as soon as possible
because my Skodavia is already one
year old and I want to get that
car repaired and
give it a new life as soon as possible.  So let's see
what happens Guys.  I
will keep sharing with you whatever updates there are.  And if you have
n't seen the previous parts, there's a
link in the description.  Definitely go and
see it.  Hope you enjoyed this video.  If you
liked it, please like, comment
, share this video with your friends
and subscribe to our channel Explore With
Us.  So see you
in the next video.  Thanks till then.